Marching to the New Wonderland
Driving Exchange
Thunderbolt, speed up!
Hurricane, locate the shortest path!
Rainbow, bring out the shield!
Mr. Slowy,
these trains are amazing!
Each train has been specifically designed
to ensure that you’ll all like them.
Look out!
Tibbie,
don’t worry! I’ve got you!
I don’t want to drive Lightning Angel anymore, Mr. Slowy!
It’s too scary!
I don’t want to drive Morning Sun anymore, either.
Morning Sun does nothing.
It doesn’t suit me one bit.
Morning Sun does much more than "nothing".
It’s an incredible mechanics train.
Try out the repair button.
I don’t want to be a mechanic, though.
I want to be on the frontlines.
I want to handle logistics.
I'm not built for attacking.
I intentionally set this up for you.
Sparky, you need to learn how to watch after your friends.
Tibbie, you also need to learn how to protect everyone.
But—
Alright, let's call it a day.
The trains can turn into a house, too?
Amazing!
Yay!
We’ll rest for tonight.
Tibbie,
give the Energy Seed to Weslie for safekeeping.
What’s wrong?
The Energy Seed is gone.
What?
What should we do now?
No need to panic.
Don't you remember that I put the Energy Seed inside a safe box?
My high-tech safe box is completely break-proof
and environmentally friendly.
It can only be opened with all six of our handprints.
Wolffy taking it isn’t even a big deal, then.
Incorrect!
Just because we have the safe box
doesn’t mean it’s safe to leave the Energy Seed unattended.
Paddi,
use Hurricane to locate the Energy Seed is.
According to Hurricane’s search,
the Energy Seed is most likely to be at one of these places.
Go split up and search.
I’ll stay here and wait.
Got it.
But...
Why don’t we swap?
Yeah!
Lightning Angel is incredible!
Watch this!
This swap was a great idea.
What's that?
There it is!
The Energy Seed!
Go get it.
Huh?
Finders keepers.
Oh no, it's Wolffy!
It's alright, Tibbie.
It's time to see what Lightning Angel is capable of.
Woah!
You’re so done!
Fix up the train for me, Tibbie!
Roger that.
Wait, what?
I’m sorry,
I didn’t mean to!
Perfect.
Oh no!
Well, that was a piece of cake.
Now that we have the Energy Seed,
I can get my strength and youth back.
I can catch all the goats I want, whenever I want to.
Yay!
What kind of stupid box is this?
Don't bother.
It's Mr. Slowy’s specially invented safe box.
You can't open it.
You don't say?
Oh, I see.
I just need to collect all six of the goats’ handprints
in order to get to the Energy Seed.
You're brilliant, Wolffy!
Warning: We have been surrounded.
This is perfect!
This is all my fault.
It’s okay. We've still got Paddi and Jonie.
It's just Jonie now.
Huh?
Where did Jonie go?
Go, Jonie!
There you are.
All that’s left now is that old goat’s handprint,
and the Energy Seed will be mine.
This is my fault.
If I hadn’t wreaked havoc on the grass with Lightning Angel,
you guys wouldn’t have run into so many obstacles.
No, it’s my fault.
I shouldn't have messed around with Morning Sun so much.
There you are.
Here I come, you old goat!
Don’t hurt Mr. Slowy!
Yell all you want.
Out of my way, stupid weeds!
Watch this.
So much for being "powerful", huh?
What are you doing?
Let me go!
Help!
Unless you want to watch them get braised, steamed, and fried,
go clear the road and fix my train.
Don’t hurt them!
We’ll help you.
Hurry up, then.
Mr. Slowy was right.
I have to learn to protect everyone with courage.
I also have to learn to watch over everyone with patience.
Oh, nicely done.
That said,
is Tibbie really going to be okay with clearing the road?
She’s just a little girl.
Don’t underestimate Tibbie.
Lightning Angel is her signature train.
All done.
Wow, great job!
I'm done, too.
Finally!
Here I come, Slowy!
Huh? What's going on?
I rescued all of my friends
while I was repairing Sirius.
He took back the Energy Seed, too.
Oh, come on!
Die!
Let's go!
Magic assembly, unmatchable energy!
Goodbye, Mr. Wolffy!
I’ll be back!
Look, guys.
We’ve arrived at the Big Tree.
There’s a branch up ahead blocking our road.
I'll clear it for us.
Tibbie,
I'll do some maintenance on your Lightning Angel.
Thank you, Sparky.
It looks like they understand my aim now.
END